Guide to the Park Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- APPENDIX A: INDEX TO SELECTED CORRESPONDENCE
  - Edwards, Jonathan (1703-1758).
    - 2 ALS to Joseph Bellamy. Canaan, Conn., November 5, 1750 (Box 1)
    - ALS to Eleazar Wheelock. New Haven, September 14, 1743 (Box 1)
    - Autograph sermon. Northampton, Mass., November 2, 1742 (Box 1)
    - Notes for a sermon? Northampton, Mass., [ca. March 17, 1743] (Box 1)
    - Autograph notes on members of his family, giving names and dates of their birth, marriages, and deaths; written on leaves of his Hebrew Bible. [n.p.], undated (Box 8)
    - Autograph notes written in the margins of newspapers. [n.p.], undated (Box 8)
    - "Observations concerning the Scripture Economy of the Trinity & Covenant of Redemption." Copy in unidentified hand. [n.p.], undated (Box 8)
    - "Things to be particularly enquired into & written upon." Stockbridge, Mass., 1752 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Jonathan (1745-1853).
    - ALS to Samuel Hopkins. New Haven, October 29, 1793
    - 2 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. New Haven, January 29, 1770; March 17, 1770 (Box 1)
    - ALS to Lucy (Edwards) Woodbridge. Princeton, N.J., June 1, 1764 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Justin (1787-1853). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Andover, Mass., August 16, 1841
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.64
  - Edwards, Pierpont (1750-1826). ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Northampton, Mass., January 21, 1771 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Robert Burr Ogden (1786-1823). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Charleston, S.C., October 30, 1823 (Box 5)
  - Edwards, Sarah (Pierrepont) (1709/10-1758). ALS to Jonathan Edwards (1703-1758). Northampton, Mass., March 17, 1743 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Timothy (1669-1753). 2 Volumes of autograph sermons. East Windsor, Conn., August 31, 1718 - March 8, 1740/41 (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Timothy (1738-1813)
    - 7 ALS to Aaron Burr. Elizabethtown, N.J. and from Letter book:
      - 1771, Sep 22 (Box 1)
      - 1797, Aug 2; Oct 3 (Box 2)
      - 1798, Feb 12 (Box 2)
      - 1805, Jan 4 (Box 2)
      - 1812, Aug 29 (Box 3)
      - 1813, Apr (Box 4)
    - ALS to Jonathan Edwards (1745-1801). Stockbridge, Mass., January 12, 1788 (Box 1)
    - 11 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. From various places:
      - 1770, Mar 5; May 3; Aug 14; Oct 30 (Box 1)
      - 1771, Feb 11; May 4; Sep 4: Oct 22; Dec 5 (Box 1)
      - 1772, Apr 18; May 22 (Box 1)
    - ALS to Tapping Reeve. Stockbridge, Mass., May 26, 1775 (Box 1)
    - Letter book containing copies of letters from Timothy Edwards to various persons. Stockbridge, Mass., 1797-1813
  - Edwards, Tryon (1809-1894). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Crosse Isle, Mich., September 29, 1890 (Box 8)
    Enclosed are extracts copied from printed letters of Mrs. Abigail (Williams) Sergeant Dwight.
  - Edwards, William (1770-1851). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Brooklyn, N.Y., January 19, 1848 (Box 7)
  - Egypt Exploration Fund. ALS to Edwards A. Park, signed by Amelia B. Edwards, honorary secretary. Bristol, England, July 25, 1885 (Box 7)
    Enclosed is a receipt for money donated, same date.
  - Eichstädt, Heinrich Karl Abraham. ALS to ____. [n.p.], November 28, 1839
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.15
  - Elliott, Ebenezer (1781-1849). (Attributed author). 1 leaf from what is apparently part of the draft of a longer article on the "landed-proprietor" obsession.
  - Ely, Ezra Stiles (1786-1861). ALS to Herman Norton. Philadelphia, December 9, 1847 (Box 7)
  - Emmons, Nathanael (1745-1840), ALS to Edwards A. Park. Franklin, Mass., August 7, 1838
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.43
  - Endicott, John (ca. 1589-1665). Legal note, undated
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.1
  - Erskine, John (1721?-1803). ALS to Joseph Bellamy. Edinburgh, May 18, 1759 (Box 1)
  - Eschenburg, Johann Joachim (1743-1820)
    - ALS in German to ____. Braunschweig, July 4, 1787
    - Autograph MS notes in German on the German translation of Shakespeare texts.
  - Evarts, Jeremiah (1781-1831). ALS to John Treadwell. Boston, July 21, 1821 (Box 5)
  - Everett, Alexander Hill (1790-1847). ALS to A. J. Eustis. Boston, June 6, 1835
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.15
  - Everett, Charles Carroll (1829-1900). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Cambridge, Mass., May 3, 1879 (Box 7)
  - Everett, Edward (1794-1865).
    - AL and ALS to Henry Edwards. Boston.
      - [September 14, 1860] (Box 8)
      - January 11, 1864
  - Eversley, Charles Shaw-Lefevre, viscount (1794-1888). ALS to Jones (name not given). [n.p.], undated
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.49
  - Farragut, David Glasgow (1801-1870). ALS to Amory Edwards. Norfolk [Va.], May 30, 1848
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.56
  - Farrar, Samuel (1784-1864).
    - Autograph copy of letter to Arthur Tappan. Andover, Mass., August 29, 1833 (Box 6)
    - Biographal data on Samuel Farrar. [n.p.], undated (Box 8)
  - Field, David Dudley (1781-1867). Certification to the licensing of Nathanael Emmons as preacher, as noted in the Records of the South Association of Hartford County, Oct 3, 1769. Haddam, Conn., March 20, 1840 (Box 7)
  - Filmore, Millard, pres. U.S. (1800-1874). ALS to Messrs. Weare C. Little & Co. of Buffalo [N.Y.], January 27, 1854
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.56
  - Fisher, Alexander Metcalf (1794-1822). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Franklin, Mass., October 6, 1815 (Box 4)
  - Fisher, George Park (1827-1909). ALS to Edwards A. Park. New Haven, February 23, 1873 (Box 7)
  - Fitch, Eleazar Thompson (1791-1871). 2 ALS to Samuel Farrar. New Haven, October 21, November 11, 1817 (Box 5)
  - Flamm. ALS in German to Bela Bates Edwards. Dusseldorf, Germany, October 10, 1846 (Box 7)
  - Forbes, John (1802-1898). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Aberdeen, Scotland, May 1, 1872 (Box 7)
  - Foster, John (1770-1843). ALS to Jonathan Edwards Ryland. [Stapleton, Gloucestershire], [undated, but probably before 1835]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.23
  - Fouqué, Friedrich, Baron de la Motte (1777-1843). Autograph poem in German, signed. Halle, Day after Good Friday, 1834
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.19
  - France. Départment de la Guerre. Document in French signed by Comte Pierre Antoine Noël Bruno Caru. Printed form filled in. Paris, February 5, 1800
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.17
  - France. Ministére de la Guerre. Letter in French signed by Alexandre Berthie to ____. Printed form filled in. Paris, March 8, 1804
  - Fraser, Alexander Campbell (1819-1914). 2 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Edinburgh, November 12, 1869; August 4, 1870 (Box 7)
  - French, Jonathan (1740-1809). List of books in an unidentified hand for a course in divinity recommended by the Rev. Johnathan French. Andover, Mass., 1813 (Box 4)
  - Frisbie, Levi (1748-1806). ALS to Eleasar Wheelock. Ipswich, Mass., November 27, 1775
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.27
  - Fuller, Anna. ALS to Agnes Park. Boston, January 28, [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Gale, Benjamin (1715-1790). ALS to Captain Riley. Killingworth [Conn.], December 1786
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.10
  - Gale, Mary. Confession of faith, signed. [n.p.], undated
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.13
  - Gallaudet, Thomas Hopkins (1787-1851). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Hartford, Conn., October 19, 1819 (Box 5)
  - Garde Nationale de Paris. Military order in French issued to Henry Edwards after the July Revolution of 1830. Printed form filled in. Paris, August 17, 1830 (Box 6)
  - Garfield, James Abram, pres. U.S. (1831-1881). ALS to Olin A. Barnard. Mentor, Ohio, July 15, 1880 (Box 7)
  - Gasparin, Agnénor Étienne, comte de (1810-1871). ALS and copy of ALS in French to ____. Rivage, Switzerland, December 17, 1861
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.53, 54
  - Gates, Horatio (1728/29-1806). ALS to Mr. Gray. [Fishkill, N.Y.], May 30, 1778
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.18
  - Gavazzi, Alexandre (1809-). ALS to Thomas A. Farnsworth. New York, August 4, 1853
  - Geoffroy Saint Hilaire, Étienne (1772-1844). ALS in French to Mme Mojon. Muséum d'Historie Naturelle, [March 27, 1836]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.50
  - Georg, duke of Braunschweig-Lunegurg (1582-1641). Military document in German. Hildesheim, Germany, April 19, 1636
  - Gilfillan, George (1813-1878). ALS to an unnamed person. Dundee, September 22, 1853
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.51
  - Gill, Sarah (Prince) (fl. 1753-1770).
    - AL (signed "Fidelia") to Aaron Burr (1715/16-1757). Boston, March 27, 1753
    - 7 ALS to Timothy Edwards. Boston:
      - 1764, July 24, 30; September 28 (Box 1)
      - 1765, June 12 (Box 1)
      - 1766, April 15; June 30 (Box 1)
      - 1770, October 31 (Box 1)
    - 2 ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Boston?:
      - 1767, April 18 (Box 1)
      - undated (Box 8)
    - AL (draft) to an unnamed person. Boston, [ca. March 1768]?
  - Glatz, Jacob (1776-1831). ALS in German to Campe. Vienna, Austria, December 3, 1822
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.68
  - Glennie, the Misses. Letter in the third person to Mr. Thane? Galleries, April 25, [n.y.]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.47
  - Goodrich, Chauncey Allen (1790-1860). ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. New Haven, January 15, 1832 (Box 6)
  - Gough, John Bartholomew (1817-1886). 2 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Worchester, Mass:, August 7, 26, 1873 (Box 7)
  - Graham, Thomas (1805-1869). AL in third person to Charles Tilt. London, February 27, 1857 (Box 7)
  - Grandpierre, Jean Henri (1799-1874). ALS in French to Frédéric Monod. Versailles, September 16, [1832]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.58
  - Gray, Asa (1810-1888). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Cambridge, Mass., October 29, 1879 (Box 7)
  - Gt. Brit. Chancellor of the Exchequer.
    - Order for payment to Dr. James Liddesdale, signed by Robert Walpole, William S. Quintin, Daniel Finch, and Thomas Newport. London, October 1715
    - Order on the commissioners of the treasury in favor of Augustus Schultz. Signed by Sir Thomas Pelham-Halles, 1st duke of Newcastle, and Henry Bilson Legge. Court of St. James, January 21, 1775
  - Gt. Brit. Sovreigns, Etc., (1738-1820) (George III). Patent in German of promotion fo Carl Gottfried Sittig from second lieutenant to first lieutenant in the British Army. Signed by George III at St. James' Palace, August 3, 1762 (Box 1)
  - Green, Ashbel (1762-1848). ALS to the Rev. William A. McDowell. Philadelphia, April 6, 1824 (Box 5)
  - Greene, Nathanael (1742-1786). LS to Nathaniel Hubbard. Camp Precaness, July 10, 1780
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.22
  - Greenleaf, Simon (1783-1853).
    - ALS to Edwards A. Park. Andover, Mass., March 7, 1849 (Box 7)
    - ALS to the Rev. Edwards A. Park. Cambridge, [Mass.], May 25, 1852
  - Grundermann, R.
    - ALS in German to Edwards A. Park. Frankfurt, Germany, August 2, 1864 (Box 7)
    - ALS to David Werthington Simon. Frankfurt, Germany, July 9, 1864 (Box 7)
  - Gurney, Anna (1795-1857). AL (signed with initials) to Mrs. Turner? [n.p.], [1852 August pencilled on]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.46
  - Gurney, Joseph John (1788-1847). ALS to an unnamed person. Norwich [Eng.], May 20, 1810
  - Guthrie, Thomas (1803-1873). ALS to Mrs. Nairn. Brechin, Scot., August 15, 1871 (Box 7)
  - Hackett, James Henry (1800-1871). Note in the third person to Mr. Porter, one of the brothers who were proprietors of the Washington Institute in New York. [n.p.], Mon, November 14, [n.y.]
  - Hale, Edward Everett (1822-1909).
    - 3 ALS to Edwards A. Park. Boston and Roxbury, Mass.
      - December 26, 1878; May 27, 1880 (Box 7)
      - December 28, 1898 (Box 8)
  - Hale, Sara Josepha (Buell) (1788-1879). ALS to M. Chamberlain, Jr. Boston, March 27, 1840
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.41
  - Halifax, Charles Montagu, 1st earl of, (1661-1715). Signature to a brief document in Latin. [n.p.], January 26, 1704
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.1
  - Hall, Anna Maria (Fielding). Note in the third person to an unnamed person who had made a gift to the Aged Governesses Asylum. [n.p.], [undated]
  - Hamilton, Alexander (1757-1804). AL in the third person to Mr. Petit. [n.p.], May 23, [n.y.]
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.10
  - Hamilton, J. ALS to Edwards A. Park. Edinburgh, November 23, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Hanna, Ann S. (Chalmers). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Edinburgh, [1869] (Box 7)
  - Harkness, Albert (1822-1907). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Providence, R.I., April 25, 1873 (Box 7)
  - Harris, John (1802-1856). ALS to an unnamed person. Geshunt College, Nerts., England, May 10, 1849? (Box 7)
  - Harrison, William Henry, pres. U.S. (1773-1841). ALS to Gov. Return Jonathan Meigs. Franklinton, Ohio, January 23, 1813
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.48
  - Harvard University. Corporation. Acknowledgment signed by Jared Sparks, president, and Thaddeus William Harris, librarian, to Edwards A. Park for a gift recieved for Harvard Library. Printed form filled in. Cambridge, Mass., January 21, 1850 (Box 7)
  - Harvard University. Students. "Petition of certain Seniors against certain restrictions at Commencement 1798." Cambridge, Mass. (Box 2)
  - Hase, Karl Benedict (1780-1864).
    - ALS in German to ____. [n.p.], August 1, [n.y.] (Box 8)
    - Social note in third person in French to ____. [n.p.], Saturday, December 19, [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Haug, Johann Christoph Friedrich (1761-1829). Autograph poem, "Friedhof-phantasie," written in German; unsigned. [n.p.], [undated]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.9
  - Hayden, Zira. Receipt to Fisher Ames in the latter's hand but signed by Hayden. Dedham [Mass.], April 16, 1795
  - Hazard, Evenezer (1744-1817). ALS to Samuel Hopkins. New York, December 10, 1788
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.25
  - Hazard, Rowland Gibson (1801-1888). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Peacedale, R.I., July 18, 1877 (Box 7)
  - Henderson, Evenexer (1784-1858)
    - ALS probably to Bela Bates Edwards. Highbury, Eng., May 30, 1846 (Box 7)
    - ALS to Samuel Plumber. Holloway [Middx.], November 7, 1837
    - ALS to Ralph Wardlaw. Highbury, Eng., June 10, 1846 (Box 7)
    - 2 ALS to unnamed persons. Highbury, Eng., June 10, 1846; April 13, 1847 (Box 7)
  - Hewit, Nathaniel (1788-1867). 2 ALS to Samuel Farrar. Fairfield, Conn., 1827, September 4; November 30 (Box 6)
  - Hill, Rowland (1744-1833). ALS to Mr. Webber. Wotton, Glos. Eng., November 3 [n.y.] (Box 8)
  - Hillhouse, James Abraham (1789-1841). ALS to Samuel J. Hitchcock, cor. sec. of the Yale chapter of Phi Beta Kappa. [New Haven], August 10, 1824
  - Hitchcock, Edward (1793-1864). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Amherst, Mass., February 15, 1836
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.58
  - Hitchcock, Roswell Dwight (1817-1887). ALS to Edwin C. Bissel. New York, April 4, 1876 (Box 7)
  - Hoar, Ebenezer Rockwood (1816-1895). ALS to E.G. Porter. Boston, October 7, 1881 (Box 7)
  - Hoare, Sir Richard Cold, 2nd bart. (1758-1838). ALS, apparently to a bookseller. Stourhead [Wilts.], [undated]
  - Hobart, John Henry (1775-1830). ALS to an unnamed person. [n.p.], Wednesday [n.y.]
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.56
  - Hodge, Charles (1797-1878). 4 ALS to Benjamin B. Wisner. Princeton, N.J.:
    - November 26, 1823
    - September 1, 1829 (Box 6)
    - May 6, 1833 (Box 6)
    - February 2, 1835 (Box 6)
  - Hogg, James (1770-1835). ALS to an unnamed person. Altrive Lake, March 19, 1834
  - Hoehne, C. J. T.(?). ALS to Edwards A. Park(?). Berlin, Germany, April 11, 1864 (Box 7)
  - Holden, Horace. ALS to Samuel Fisher. New York, November 26, 1822
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.55
  - Holland, Barbara. "Lines inscribed to the memory of the first Christian Martyrs who suffered in the earliest persecution of Nero." [n.p.], [undated]
  - Holland, Henry Richard Vassall Fox, 3rd baron (1773-1840). ALS to an unnamed person. Middleton, August 2, [n.y.]
  - Holmes, Abiel (1763-1837). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Cambridge, Mass., May 23, 1821 (Box 5)
  - Holmes, George. Last will and testament signed with his mark; in the hand of and witnessed by John Eliot and John ____?. Not dated, but certified to before the County Court of Suffolk County, Mass. Nov 30, 1657? by John Eliot as about the year 1646.
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.5
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (1809-1894).
    - ALS to William Edwards Park. Boston, April 18, 1882 (Box 7)
    - ALS to an unnamed person. Boston, May 18, 1887 (Box 7)
  - Home. Letter in the third person to Mr. Glyde. British Museum, February 11, 1851
  - Homer, Jonathan (1759-1843). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Newton, Mass., April 15, 1818 (Box 5)
  - Hopkins, Mark (1802-1877). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Williamstown, Mass., November 1, 1837
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.30
  - Hopkins, Samuel (1721-1803).
    - ALS (draft) to Aaron Burr. Newport, [no month or day] 1802
    - ALS (draft) to John Erskine. Newport, January 14, 1789
    - ALS (draft) to Granville Sharp. Newport, January 16, 1789
    - "Subjects for meditation, prayer and praise observed by Miss Susanna Anthony on particular days of the week." Unsigned. [n.p.] (Box 8)
  - Howells, William Dean (1837-1920). ALS to Olin A. Brainard. Boston, January 13, 1880 (Box 7)
  - Howson, John Saul (1816-1885). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Chester, Eng., July 18, 1872 (Box 7)
  - Humboldt, Alexder, Freiherr von (1769-1859). Copy of letter in French to Thomas Chase. [n.p.], [undated] (Box 8)
  - Humphrey, Heman (1779-1861). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Hatfield, Mass., July 7, 1845
  - Hunt, Eunice (Edwards) Pollock (1743-?). ALS to Sarah (Burr) Reeve. Elizabethtown, N.J., January 5, 1778 (Box 1)
  - Hunt, Wilson Price (1782?-1842). Bill of exchange drawn on John Jacob Astor in favor of Hougua. Canton, China, March 26, 1816 (Box 4)
  - Huntington, Samuel (1731-1796). Autograph copy, signed, of letter to Thomas Jefferson. Norwich, [Conn.], March 25, 1793
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.6
  - Hutton, Richard Holt (1826-1897). ALS to an unnamed person. London, [undated] (Box 8)
  - Irving, John Treat (1778-1838). ALS to Edward Cutts, Jr. New York, January 27, 1814
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.4
  - Irving, Washington (1783-1859). AL (signed with initials) to George Palmer Putman. [n.p.], [undated]
  - Jackson, Andrew, pres. U.S. (1767-1845) ALS to James Monroe. Washington, January 15, 1824
  - Jacobus, Melanchton Williams (1816-1876). ALS to William F. Allen. Allegheny, Pa., March 18, 1871 (Box 7)
  - Jacoby, Ludwig S. Receipt to Edwards A. Park. Bremen, Germany, August 19, [1869]? (Box 7)
  - James, B. V. ALS to Abijah R. Baker. Fair Hope, Cape Palmas, N. Africa, June 15, 1839 (Box 6)
  - James, George Payne Rainsford (1799-1860). ALS to an unnamed person. New Haven, Conn., October 27, 1850
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.30
  - Jay, John (1745-1829). ALS to Peter Van Schaack. Bath [Eng.], December 21, 1783
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.10
  - Jefferson, Thomas, pres. U.S. (1743-1826). AL in the third person to Dr. S. L. Mitchell. Washington, May 21, 1805
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.36
  - Jenks, William (1778-1866). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Boston, May 9, 1842 (Box 7)
  - Jervis, Thomas Best. ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Kensington, Eng., June 20, 1846 (Box 7)
  - Johnson, Richard Mentor (1780-1850). ALS to Langdon Cheves. [Washington], March 25, 1822
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.48
  - Johnson, W.A. ALS to Edwards A. Park. London, July 23, 1869 (Box 7)
  - Jomini, Henri, baron (1779-1869). Note in French of furniture given to Frédéric Joél Jean Gérard Monod by Jomini; signed by Jomini. Paris, May 16, 1820
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.55
  - Jones, Charles Colcock (1804-1863). ALS to the Rev. A. R. Baker. Philadelphia, February 21, 1853 (Box 7)
  - Joseph Bonaparte, King of Spain (1768-1844).
    - AL signed Joseph Survigli to Messrs. LeRoy, Bayard and McEvers. New York, November 29, 1815 (Box 4)
    - LS in French to ____. signed Alphonse Lejambe [pseud]. Pointe Breye[?], April 21, 1820
  - Judd, Adeline (Rossiter). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Lake Forest, Ill., January 4, 1884 (Box 7)
  - Judson, Adoniran (1788-1850). Note expressing regards to Lucius Bolles, apparently sent with something. Maulmein, Burma, April 7, 1843
    See: box 10, folder 120, v.4, p.53
  - Jullien, A[uguste] (d. 1854?). ALS to Ducoudray Holstein. Paris, July 20, 1829
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.66
  - Kamehameha III, King of the Sandwich Islands (1814-1854). ALS in Hawaiian to Lister Armstrong (E. Limaikaika). Honolulu, Hawaii, April 5, 1854 (Box 7)
  - Kane, Elisha Kent (1820-1857). Minutes of his practice in the Philadelphia Hospital," i.e. clinical notes on patients one of whom is given as Moses Welch, age 57. Unsigned. [n.p.], [undated]
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.55
  - Kelvin, William Thompson, baron (1824-1907). ALS to John Ker (1819-1886?). Largs, Scotland, October 13, 1871 (Box 7)
  - Kent, James (1763-1847). AL in the third person to Messrs. William Gould & Co. Albany, January 9, 1818
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.34
  - King, Jonas (1792-1869). 2 ALS to Samuel Farrar. New York, November 2, 1827; November 26 1827 (Box 6)
  - King, Rufus (1755-1827). Recognizance in the case of Anthony Knap to the Commonwealth of Mass., Supreme judicial court. Nov 6, 1781. Justice's court, Essex section, October 17, 1781
    See: box 9, folder 118, v.2, p.18
  - Kingsley, James Luce (1782-1852). ALS to the Rev. Edwards A. Park. New Haven, August 23, 1852
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.13
  - Kirkland, Caroline Matilda (Stansbury) (1801-1864). ALS to John Stilwell Jenkins. New York, May 15, 1847
    See: box 9, folder 117, v.1, p.57
  - Kirkland, John Thornton (1770-1840). 2 ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. Cambridge, Mass., January 7, 1818; June 12, 1819 (Box 5)
  - Knox, Lucy (Flucker) (1756-1824). ALS to Lucy Flucker (Knox) Thatcher. Boston, June 18, 1806 (Box 3)
  - Knox, William Shabrach (1843-1914). TLS to Agnes Park. Washington, May 21, 1900 (Box 8)
  - Kuhner, Rafael (1802-1878). ALS to Bela Bates Edwards. Magdeburg, Germany, October 4, 1846 (Box 7)
  - Lagarde, Paul Anton de (1827-1891). Autograph postcard signed to Edwards A. Park. Göttingen, Germany, December 7, 1878 (Box 7)
  - Laharpe, Henry. ALS in French to Mme. Wolff. [n.p.], Saturday, [1846?] (Box 7)
  - Lamartine, Alphonse Marie Louis (1790-1869). ALS in French to ____. Paris, Feb, 1856
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.33
  - Lancaster, Joseph (1773-1838). ALS to Joseph Dell, Sr. [London], September 12, 1811
  - Langvein, August Freidrich Ernst (1757-1835). ALS in German to ____. Berlin, Germany, July 26, 1816
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.24
  - Lansdowne, Sir Henry Petty-FitzMaurice, 3rd Marquis of (1780-1863). ALS to an unnamed person. [London], March 13, [n.y.]
    See: box 9, folder 119, v.3, p.45
  - Larned, Sylvester (1796-1820). ALS to Samuel Farrar. Pittsfield, Mass., December 22, 1814 (Box 4)
  - Lathrop, John (1740-1816). Certification to the marriage of Thomas Fennerce [i.e. Fennecy] and Elizabeth Loring on Nov 26, 1778. Boston, November 21, 1782
  - Lathrop, Joseph (1731-1820). ALS to Eliphalet Pearson. West Springfield, Mass., February 21, 1795 (Box 2)
  - Lawrence, William (1850-1941). TLS to Agnes Park. Boston, January 19, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves Roch Gilbert du Motier, Marquis de (1757-1834). ALS to an unnamed person. La Orange [France], October 1826
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.26
  - Lee, Henry (1756-1818). ALS to Col. Rhea. Philadelphia, December 16, 1802
    See: box 10, folder 122, v.6, p.30
  - Leo, Heinrich (1799-1878). Announcement written in German of his lecture schedule during the semester beginning Oct 22. [n.p.], October 22, [n.y.]
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.29
  - Leonhard, Gustav (1816-1878). Letter of introduction in German to Dr. Kaup at Darmstadt. Heidelburg, October 19, 1842
    See: box 10, folder 121, v.5, p.20
  - Lieber, Francis (1800-1872). ALS to Edwards A. Park. Columbia, S.C., March 6, 1851 (Box 7)
  - Lightfoot, Joseph Barber (1828-1889). ALS to Edwards A. Park. London, September 9, 1871 (Box 7)